MUSKAN **SHARMA**

Gurugram, India 122003 | +91 7310739647 | muskansharma.ms797@gmail.com | **WWW:** http://www.linkedin.com/in/muskan-sharma-3a87a020

Summary

Proven Account Manager with a track record of driving growth and enhancing client satisfaction at GreyB Research. Expert in leveraging data analysis and market research to identify opportunities, coupled with exceptional problem-solving skills to deliver strategic solutions. Increased partner revenue by 20%, showcasing strong analytical abilities and a commitment to excellence.

Work Experience

Account Manager/Customer Success Representative GreyB Research

09/2024 to Current Gurugram, India

- Serve as the primary point of contact for assigned client accounts, understanding their goals, needs, and challenges.
- Develop and execute strategic account plans to drive growth, enhance client satisfaction, and maximize revenue.
- Conduct regular face-to-face business reviews with clients, analyzing performance metrics and identifying areas for improvement.
- Track and analyze account performance, sales data, and market trends to identify opportunities for expansion and optimization.
- Drive business growth for newly onboarded partners by improving key operational and performance metrics.
- Increase incremental revenue through effective monetization strategies and commercial enhancements.
- Expand counter share for assigned clients by implementing strategic initiatives to dominate market share.

Sales Development Representative, Inside Sales GreyB Research

08/2023 to 08/2024 Gurugram, India

- Lead Generation and Prospecting, Discovery and Qualification, Product Introduction
- Identify potential customers and generate new business opportunities for the company
- Contact and qualify potential customers
- Set appointments and follow up on leads
- Track progress towards meeting sales goals
- Collaborate with the sales team to develop strategies for reaching sales targets
- Build long-term trusting relationships with prospects
- Extensive experience using SaaS products like BOS, FIT, Slate, SlatePro
- Collaborated with Marketing teams to drive lead engagement and conversion within the sales funnel.

Research Associate (Market Research) SPER RESEARCH

12/2022 to 06/2023

Noida. India

- Analyzed data using statistical software including SPSS, Excel, R, Python.
- Utilized leading market research tools, including Nielsen, Ipsos, GfK, and Kantar.
- Gathering and interpreting data from these platforms to inform decision-making
- Data Visualization: insightful data visualizations using tools like Tableau, Power BI, or Google Data Studio
- Market Research Techniques: market research techniques, such as conjoint analysis, regression modeling, factor analysis, cluster analysis, or A/B testing
- Primary Research and Secondary Research
- Qualitative and Quantitative Research

INDIAN BIOLOGICAL AND RESEARCH INSTITUTE

- Database Analysis Using Python
- Implemented Drug Designing Treatment For Cataract
- Stacks Learnt: Molecular Docking, Bioinformatics Tools Such As Cytoscape, String, Molegro, PYRX, Python, Database Analysis, Drug Designing, Consumer Space

Education

Bachelor in Technology + Master in Technology Integrated Course: Biotechnology

01/2023

JAYPEE INSTITUTE OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Noida, India

GPA: 7.1

H.S.C: PCB
DELHI PUBLIC SCHOOL

05/2017 Aligarh, India

Certifications

- HubSpot Inbound Sales
- Sales Enablement
- Sales Management
- Inbound
- Frictionless Sales

Projects

Major Project, Jaypee Institute of Information Technology, Noida, Uttar Pradesh, Investigation of Multi component Interactions For Anti-Aging Properties of Mushroom Cosmetics., Python, C++, Preparation of Library Ligand, Molecular Docking by using PYRX Tool, Prediction of Binding Affinity

Minor Project, Jaypee Institute of Information Technology, Noida, Uttar Pradesh, Worked on PROTEOGENOMICS and MiRNA Vaccines., Working on Collaborative Environment, Teamwork And Analytical Skills, Project Processes, Data Analysis, Primary And Secondary Research

Key Skills

- Time Management, Communication, Confident, Analytical, Passionate, Efficient
- Problem-solving skills, Ability to work with ambiguous tasks, Find suitable solutions, P&L
 Understanding, Market Research and Intelligence, Customer Lifetime Value, Business Development,
 Data Logic, Data Interpretation, Data Visualization
- Data Analysis, Result Orientation, Managing Relationships, Conflict Management, Problem-Solving, Seek help/advice where appropriate.
- Ability to work independently and within a team framework
- Lead Generation, CRM Proficiency, Outbound and Inbound Sales, Lead Qualification
- Business Intelligence, Proactive approach to achieving success, Client Relationships

Technical Skills

 SQL, Python, MS PowerPoint, MS Excel, MS Word, Outlook, Power BI, C++, Bioinformatics Tools (AutoDock Vena, Cytoscape, String, Molegro, PYRX), Process Writing, LinkedIn Sales Navigator, Zoominfo, Lusha, Apollo, Rocket Reach, CRM Tools (HubSpot, Salesforce).

Languages

English: First Language

Accomplishments

LinkedIn Recommendation Received